let's get creative today because it's a DIY crafting video you may know
these belts from my styling videos because I use them quite often and every
time I use them I get the question where can I buy these and then I'm answering
they're self-made and then people are disappointed because they can't buy them
so I'm going to show you how to do them yourself I will put some information in
the description text box below the video where you can find the individual parts
you of course need a metal belt and then I have some rings and metal parts for example a gold
one with a golden u-piece or the pre-assembled o-ring here but I also have bigger and smaller
rings which can be fit together or yeah put together like this so you have various options
to create your own look. So today I'm going to make a belt with this o-ring
part here. This is a 30 millimeter silver belt and these are not lockable. That's
also a question I always get. But before I drill a hole in it I'm going to check
if it fits and which clasp I would close it. So the last one I guess.
and I'll put a piece of tape over the middle and the front.
Should be around here.
Now that I put down a piece of tape, I'll take a permanent marker and make a cross in the middle.
Around here.
I'll put the belt over a piece of wood here
and use a center puncher to make a dent in the metal.
Whoop.
slippery. Now I can use my mini drill and put it in the dent here and drill
through the metal. I left the piece of tape and the plastic wrap on the belt so
I'm not scratching it and I hope the hole is smoother that way.
In case you're wondering why I'm able to drill a hole with this mini machine here,
this is not a steel belt but brass.
Now the most satisfying part, peeling off the plastic wrap.
If you have a deburrer tool that is small enough, you can use it here.
Unfortunately this one is big and my hole is too small.
I have my O-ring for the front and for the back I have a tiny screw which I'm simply
going to screw together now.
This is the finished belt.
It's obviously the easiest one of them.
If you want to have a complexer design with these kind of U pieces then you have to drill
holes for each of these sides here and put smaller screws from the back side
here and with these you can hold the rings in place okay if you have any
questions let me know in the comments I hope you enjoyed this tutorial and I
I will see you in the next video.
Have a nice day.
Bye.
is what we call the night
I can't be this way before the night
Thank you.